A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Cox and Reece Investigations FA418
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Digest Files, 1; 13.54 Cubic Feet 22 letter document boxes and 11 legal document boxes
  - Individuals, 1
    - 128 - Heretick, Stefan, 1947-1949 (Box 9, Folder 191)
    - 129 - Tuzar, Jaroslav, 1947-1949 (Box 9, Folder 192)
    - 130 - Hubert, Stanislaw L., 1935 (Box 9, Folder 193)
    - 131 - Chalasinski, Dr. Joseph, 1930-1952 (Box 9, Folder 194)
    - 132 - Sorensen, Hans Christian, 1947-1952 (Box 9, Folder 195)
    - 133 - Lederer, Dr. Edgar, 1950-1952 (Box 9, Folder 196)
    - 134 - Zawadski, Dr. Bohdan, Zebrowkska, Tadeusz, 1936-1952 (Box 9, Folder 197)
    - 135 - Lange, Oscar, 1933-1954 (Box 9, Folder 198)
    - 136 - Balogh, Thomas, 1947-1952 (Box 9, Folder 199)
    - 137 - Maiwald, Karel, 1928-1952 (Box 9, Folder 200)
    - 138 - De Francis, John, 1942-1952 (Box 9, Folder 201)
    - 139 - Eisler, Hanns, 1939-1954 (Box 9, Folder 202)
    - 140 - Robin, Harry L., 1939-1952 (Box 9, Folder 203)
    - 142 - Tzoncheff, Tzonu S. et. al. (Bulgarian), 1931-1952 (Box 9, Folder 204)
    - 143 - Lovestone, Jay, 1948-1951 (Box 9, Folder 205)
    - 144 - Hughes, Langston, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 206)
    - 145 - Read, Nicholas C., 1939-1952 (Box 9, Folder 207)
    - 146 - Grierson, John, 1938-1952 (Box 9, Folder 208)
    - 147 - Baykov, Alexander (Russian), 1938-1952 (Box 10, Folder 209)
    - 148 - Brachet, Jean Louis, 1936-1952 (Box 10, Folder 210)
    - 149 - Romein, J. M., 1949-1952 (Box 10, Folder 211)
    - 150 - Bernardelli, Harro, 1934-1952 (Box 10, Folder 212)
    - 151 - Winter, Robert, 1936-1952 (Box 10, Folder 213)
    - 152 - Bisson, Thomas A., 1936-1954 (Box 10, Folder 214)
    - 153 - Filipovic, Milenko S., 1939-1952 (Box 10, Folder 215)
    - 154 - Clarke, Alan D. B., 1950-1952 (Box 10, Folder 216)
    - 155 - Joliot - Curie, Frederic, 1935-1954 (Box 10, Folder 217)
    - 156 - Bottomore, Thomas B., 1950-1954 (Box 10, Folder 218)
    - 157 - Rosinger, L. K., 1939-1954 (Box 10, Folder 219)
    - 158 - Skelj, Bozo, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 220)
    - 159 - Tomsic, Ivan, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 221)
    - 160 - Murra, John, 1948-1952 (Box 10, Folder 222)
    - 161 - Adamic, Louis, 1936-1954 (Box 11, Folder 223)
    - 162 - Catunda, Omar, 1944-1952 (Box 11, Folder 224)
    - 163 - Tomasevich, Jozo, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 225)
    - 164 - Hallie Flanagan Davis: Drama Studies, 1937-1953 (Box 11, Folder 226)
    - 165 - Yanaihara, Tadao, 1950-1952 (Box 11, Folder 227)
    - 166 - Chen, Han - seng, 1945-1954 (Box 11, Folder 228)
    - 167 - Fairbank, Wilma (wife of John K, Fairbank), 1943-1952 (Box 11, Folder 229)
    - 168 - Chi, Chao - ting, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 230)
    - 169 - Simmons, Ernest J.: Columbia University: Slavic Studies, 1947-1954 (Box 11, Folder 231)
    - 169A - Simmons, E. J.: American Slavic and East European Review, 1937-1952 (Box 11, Folder 232)
    - 169B - Simmons, Ernest J.: American Council of Learned Studies, 1943-1952 (Box 11, Folder 233)
    - 170 - Beznak, A. B.: Hungarian Biological Research Institute: Tihany, 1945-1952 (Box 11, Folder 234)
    - 170A - Beznak, A. B., 1925-1949 (Box 11, Folder 235)
    - 171 - Bernal, J. D.: Birkbeck College: X - ray Analysis, 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 236)
    - 172 - Fairbank, John K., 1934-1954 (Box 11, Folder 237)
    - 173 - 1 - Yakobson, Sergius, 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 238)
    - 174 - Carter, Edward C., 1937-1952 (Box 11, Folder 239)
    - 175 - Gerebtzoff, Agrege M., 1950-1952 (Box 12, Folder 240)
    - 176 - Lee, Pao - Chen, 1936-1952 (Box 12, Folder 241)
    - 177 - Kennan, George, 1948-1952 (Box 12, Folder 242)
    - 178 - Jasny, Naum: Stanford University: Soviet Economic Development, 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 243)
    - 179 - Oster, Gerald, 1946-1952 (Box 12, Folder 244)
    - 180 - Westergaaard, Mogens, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 245)
    - 181 - Muller, Hermann J., 1935-1951 (Box 12, Folder 246)
    - 182 - Carter, Edward J., 1941-1952 (Box 12, Folder 247)
    - 183 - Kautsky, Benedikt, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 248)
    - 184 - Viden, Ivan: Adamec, Cenek, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 249)
    - 185 - Roucek, Frantisek, 1959-1972 (Box 12, Folder 250)
    - 186 - Rajchman, Ludwik, 1930-1952 (Box 12, Folder 251)
    - 187 - Imbriotis, Rosa, 1929-1952 (Box 12, Folder 252)
    - 188 - Deutscher, Isaac, 1948-1952 (Box 12, Folder 253)
    - 189 - Pauling, Linus C.: California Institute of Technology, 1932-1954 (Box 12, Folder 254)
    - 190 - Kemey, George, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 255)
    - 191 - Belshaw, Horace, 1934-1952 (Box 12, Folder 256)
    - 192 - Monod, Jacques L., 1935-1954 (Box 12, Folder 257)
    - 193 - Saraiva, Paulo, 1948-1952 (Box 12, Folder 258)
    - 194 - Machotka, Otakar, 1934-1952 (Box 12, Folder 259)
    - 195 - Reischauer, Edwin O., 1945 (Box 12, Folder 260)
    - 196 - Matthiessen, Francis O., 1943-1952 (Box 12, Folder 261)
    - 197 - Fryckstedt, Olov. W., 1947-1952 (Box 12, Folder 262)
    - 198 - Van der Sprenkel, Otto, 1949-1955 (Box 12, Folder 263)
    - 199 - Garbacik, Eugene, 1947-1948 (Box 12, Folder 264)
    - 200 - Lipinski, Edward, 1934-1952 (Box 12, Folder 265)
    - 201 - Pilczuk, Peter, 1946-1952 (Box 13, Folder 266)
    - 202 - Fiala, Silvio, 1946-1952 (Box 13, Folder 267)
    - 203 - Schober, Bruno, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 268)
    - 204 - Fry, Varian, 1940-1952 (Box 13, Folder 269)
    - 205 - Bonner, David M., 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 270)
    - 206 - Draper, Theodore, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 271)
    - 207 - Caughey, John W., 1950-1954 (Box 13, Folder 272)
    - 208 - Krebs, Hans A., 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 273)
    - 209 - Chain, E. B., 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 274)
    - 210 - Florkin, Marcel, 1947-1952 (Box 13, Folder 275)
    - 211 - Cohen, Georges N., 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 276)
    - 212 - 1 - Bergestraesser, Arnold, 1941-1943 (Box 13, Folder 277)
    - 213 - Rypackova, Anna, 1946-1952 (Box 13, Folder 278)
    - 214 - Krylenko, Eliena, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 279)
    - 215 - Bodde, Derk, 1938-1952 (Box 13, Folder 280)
    - 216 - Einaudi, Mario: Cornell University: French and Italian Political and Economic Issues, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 281)
    - 217 - Bussard, Alain, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 282)
    - 218 - Grabar, Pierre: Pasteur Institute, Paris, 1932-1952 (Box 13, Folder 283)
    - 219 - Luthy, Bertha B., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 284)
    - 220 - Odlozilik, Otakar, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 285)
    - 221 - Brunauer, Esther C., 1946-1952 (Box 13, Folder 286)
    - 222 - Laguardia, Rafael, 1941-1952 (Box 13, Folder 287)
    - 223 - Normano, John F., 1943-1952 (Box 13, Folder 288)
    - 224 - Schnitzer, Robert C., 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 289)
    - 225 - Latouche, John, 1949-1954 (Box 13, Folder 290)
    - 226 - Alegria, Paula, 1937-1952 (Box 13, Folder 291)
    - 227 - Ruzicka, Leopold: Federal Technical Institute: Zurich, 1946-1952 (Box 13, Folder 292)
    - 228 - Dougherty, Ellsworth C., 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 293)
    - 229 - Nigon, Victor, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 294)
    - 230 - Pirie, Norman W., 1939-1952 (Box 13, Folder 295)
    - 231 - Wiesner, Karel, 1947-1952 (Box 13, Folder 296)
    - 232 - Hardman, J. B. S.: Columbia University: Labor Union Leadership, 1946-1952 (Box 13, Folder 297)
    - 233 - Hoijer, Harry, 1947-1952 (Box 13, Folder 298)
    - 234 - Needham, Joseph, 1935-1952 (Box 13, Folder 299)
    - 235 - Leyda, J., 1936-1952 (Box 13, Folder 300)
    - 236 - Rieben, Willy K., 1942-1952 (Box 13, Folder 301)
    - 237 - Waddinton, Conrad H., 1931-1952 (Box 13, Folder 302)
    - 238 - White, Michael J. D., 1937-1952 (Box 13, Folder 303)
    - 239 - Lee, Shu - Ching, 1945-1952 (Box 13, Folder 304)
    - 240 - Sigerist, Henry: Johns Hopkins University: Institute of History of Medicine, 1935-1950 (Box 13, Folder 305)
    - 241 - Graves, Mortimer: American Council of Learned Societies: Near East Visit, 1935-1952 (Box 14, Folder 306)
    - 242 - Zlotowski, Ignace, 1940-1954 (Box 14, Folder 307)
    - 243 - Graves, Mortimer: Russian and Far East Visit: 1936: ACLS: International Study, 1935 - 1952 (Box 14, Folder 308)
    - 244 - Mann, Thomas, 1938-1954 (Box 14, Folder 309)
    - 245 - Manuila, Sabin: Institute for Communist Refugees, 1947-1950 (Box 14, Folder 310)
    - 246 - Jansen, Marius B.: Japanese Visit: 1951: Chugoku Kenkyujo (Box 14, Folder 311)
    - 247 - Toynbee, Arnold: Royal Institute of International Affairs, 1941-1952 (Box 14, Folder 312)
    - 248 - Horkheimer, Max: Institute for Social Research, Frankfurt, 1932-1952 (Box 14, Folder 313)
    - 249 - Weil, Andre, 1926-1952 (Box 14, Folder 314)
    - 250 - Hadamard, Jacques, 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 315)
    - 251 - Szent - Gyorgyi, Albert, 1929-1954 (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - 252 - Morrison, J. A., 1937-1952 (Box 14, Folder 317)
    - 253 - Redfield, Robert, 1940-1952 (Box 14, Folder 318)
    - 254 - Trone, Sol, 1947-1951 (Box 14, Folder 319)
    - 255 - Lwoff, Andre, 1932-1952 (Box 14, Folder 320)
    - 256 - Rashba, Evsey S.: Stanford University: Soviet Law Study, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 321)
    - 257 - Loewenthal, Rudolf: Cornell University: Soviet Union Mohammedan Study, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 322)
    - 258 - Wu, Wen - tsao, 1947-1952 (Box 14, Folder 323)
    - 259 - Tolman, E. C., 1951-1954 (Box 14, Folder 324)
    - 260 - McCune, Evelyn B., 1937-1950 (Box 14, Folder 325)
    - 261 - Polanyi, Michael, 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 326)
    - 262 - Pontecorvo, Bruno, 1940-1952 (Box 14, Folder 327)
    - 263 - Mei, Y. F., 1947-1952 (Box 14, Folder 328)
    - 264 - Taylor, George E., 1941-1950 (Box 14, Folder 329)
    - 265 - Pos, Hendrik J., 1948-1952 (Box 14, Folder 330)
    - 266 - Danielli, James Frederic, 1947-1952 (Box 14, Folder 331)
    - 267 - Luria, Salvatore, 1940-1954 (Box 14, Folder 332)
    - 268 - Rapkine, Louis, 1925-1952 (Box 15, Folder 333)
    - 269 - Tiomno, Jayme, 1946-1952 (Box 15, Folder 334)
    - 270 - Teissier, G., 1938-1952 (Box 15, Folder 335)
    - 271 - Stadler, L. J., 1949-1952 (Box 15, Folder 336)
    - 272 - Aubel, Eugene, 1949-1952 (Box 15, Folder 337)
    - 273 - Pontecorvo, Guido, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 338)
    - 274 - Bittencourt, Paulo T., 1945-1952 (Box 15, Folder 339)
    - 275 - E. O. Melby, New York University Work Student Exchange Program, 1949-1952 (Box 15, Folder 340)
    - 276 - Sergio, Lisa, 1944-1952 (Box 15, Folder 341)
    - 277 - Kral, Alois, 1928-1952 (Box 15, Folder 342)
    - 278 - Gantt, W. Horsley, 1929-1952 (Box 15, Folder 343)
    - 279 - Dean, Vera Micheles, 1941-1952 (Box 15, Folder 344)
    - 280 - Joliot - Curie, Irene, 1948-1952 (Box 15, Folder 345)
    - 281 - Kennedy, George: National Peking University, 1935-1952 (Box 15, Folder 346)
    - 282 - Holland, William L., 1932-1954 (Box 15, Folder 347)
    - 283 - Macgowan, Kenneth, 1950-1954 (Box 15, Folder 348)
    - 284 - Wirth, Louis: University of Chicago: Race Relations, 1941-1952 (Box 15, Folder 349)
    - 285 - Adams, Arthur S.: American Council on Education, 1949-1952 (Box 15, Folder 350)
    - 286 - Schutzer, Walter de Camargo, 1946-1952 (Box 15, Folder 351)
    - 287 - Bissar, Farida A., 1951-1952 (Box 15, Folder 352)
    - 288 - Pope, Arthur Upham: Asia Institute, 1949-1952 (Box 15, Folder 353)
    - 289 - Gulich, Wilhelm J., 1934-1952 (Box 15, Folder 354)
    - 290 - Klineberg, Otto, 1927-1952 (Box 15, Folder 355)
    - 291 - Foreman, Clark, 1950-1959 (Box 15, Folder 356)
    - 292 - Aoyama, Hideo, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 357)
    - 293 - McLawhon, Arthur, 1951-1952 (Box 15, Folder 358)
    - 500 - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1925-1952 (Box 15, Folder 359)
    - 501 - Barnard, Chester, 1939-1952 (Box 16, Folder 360)
    - 502 - Willits, Joseph H.: Personal, 1944-1952 (Box 16, Folder 361)
    - 502A - Willits, Joseph H.: Institute of Pacific Relations, 1948-1951 (Box 16, Folder 362)
    - 502B - Willits, Joseph H., 1940-1951 (Box 16, Folder 363)
    - 503 - Rhind, Flora, 1941-1952 (Box 16, Folder 364)
    - 503A - Rhind, Flora, 1937-1946 (Box 16, Folder 365)
    - 504 - Weaver, Warren: Private, 1948-1950 (Box 16, Folder 366)
    - 504A - Weaver, Warren, 1941-1952 (Box 16, Folder 367)
    - 505 & 505A - Havighurst, Robert J., 1947-1951 (Box 16, Folder 368)
    - 506 - Fahs, Charles B.: Private, 1946-1952 (Box 16, Folder 369)
    - 506A - Fahs, Charles B., 1946-1950 (Box 16, Folder 370A)
    - 506A - Fahs, Charles B., 1946-1950 (Box 16, Folder 370B)
    - 507 - Marshall, John, 1942-1952 (Box 17, Folder 371)
    - 507A - Marhsall, John: Reports, etc., 1943-1952 (Box 17, Folder 372)
    - 507B - Marshall, John, 1939-1952 (Box 17, Folder 373)
    - 508 - Grant, John B., 1931-1952 (Box 17, Folder 374)
    - 509 - Buchanan, Norman S., 1947-1952 (Box 17, Folder 375)
    - 509A - Buchanan, Norman S., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 376)
    - 510 - DeVinny, Leland C., 1942-1952 (Box 17, Folder 377)
    - 511 - Gunn, Selskar M., 1936-1952 (Box 17, Folder 378)
    - 511A - Gunn, Selskar M., 1933 (Box 17, Folder 379)
    - 512 - Watson, Robert B., 1949-1952 (Box 17, Folder 380)
    - 512A - Watson, Robert B., 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 381)
    - 513 - Walker, Sydnor, 1950-1952 (Box 17, Folder 382)
    - 513A - Walker, Sydnor, 1936-1938 (Box 17, Folder 383)
    - 514 - Makinsky, Alexander, 1944-1954 (Box 17, Folder 384)
    - 514A - Makinsky, Alexander, 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 385)
    - 515 - Kittredge, Tracy B.: Reports, 1939-1952 (Box 17, Folder 386)
    - 516 - Oliver, Wade, 1948-1951 (Box 17, Folder 387)
    - 517 - Miller, H. M., 1935-1952 (Box 17, Folder 388)
    - 518 - O, Brien, Daniel P., 1929-1946 (Box 18, Folder 389)
    - 519 - Evans, Roger F., 1947-1950 (Box 18, Folder 390)
    - 519A - Evans, Roger F., 1942-1945 (Box 18, Folder 391)
    - 521 - Tisdale, W. E., 1938 (Box 18, Folder 392)
    - 522 - D'Arms, Edward F., 1947-1948 (Box 18, Folder 393)
    - 523 - Hanson, Frank Blair, 1935-1945 (Box 18, Folder 394)
    - 524 - Chadwell, Marshall H., 1947 (Box 18, Folder 395)
    - 525 - Berrien, William, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 396)
    - 526 - Pomerat, Gerard R., 1946-1952 (Box 18, Folder 397)
    - 527 - Leach, C. N. (Box 18, Folder 398)
    - 528 - Bauer, J. H., 1945-1948 (Box 18, Folder 399)
    - 529 - Struthers, Rolf, 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder 400)
    - 530 - Balfour, Marshall C., 1939 (Box 18, Folder 401)
    - 531 - Fitzgerald, J. G. (Box 18, Folder 402)
    - 532 - Lambert, R. A., 1932-1948 (Box 18, Folder 403)
    - 533 - Mosely, Philip E., 1950 (Box 18, Folder 404)
    - 534 - Kimball, Lindsley F.: Personal, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 405)
  - General, 2
    - 600 - National Security Problems, 1944-1952 (Box 18, Folder 406)
    - 601 - Financial Administration: Taxation, 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder 407)
    - 602-1 - Program and Policy: General, 1937-1949 (Box 18, Folder 408)
    - 603 - Program and Policy: Propaganda, 1915-1947 (Box 18, Folder 409)
    - 604 - Executive Sessions, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 410)
    - 605 - Program and Policy: Radio and Motion Pictures, 1938-1939 (Box 19, Folder 411)
    - 606 - Program and Policy: Social Sciences, 1922-1952 (Box 19, Folder 412)
    - 606A - Progam and Policy: Social Sciences: International Relations, 1935-1952 (Box 19, Folder 413)
    - 606B - Program and Policy: Social Sciences: Totalitarian Studies Conference, 1940-1941 (Box 19, Folder 414)
    - 607 - Program and Policy: Humanities, 1944-1952 (Box 19, Folder 415)
    - 608 - Progam and Policy: Social Medicine, 1936-1952 (Box 19, Folder 416)
    - 609 - Academic Freedom, 1949-1952 (Box 19, Folder 417)
    - 610 - Immigration Problems, 1948-1952 (Box 19, Folder 418)
    - 611-War: General, 1939-1952 (Box 19, Folder 419)
    - 612 - Conference on Slavic Studies, 1943-1952 (Box 19, Folder 420)
    - 613 - Critcisms and Inquiries: Subversive Activities, 1945-1951 (Box 19, Folder 421)
    - 614 - Congressional Investigations, 1950-1952 (Box 19, Folder 422)
    - 615 - Officers Conference, 1942-1950 (Box 19, Folder 423)
    - 616 - Criticism of Rockefeller Foundation, 1939-1952 (Box 19, Folder 424)
    - 617 - Memos to Counsel: Projects, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 425)
    - 618 - Memos to Counsel: Individuals, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 426)
    - 619 - United States Congress: General, 1942-1948 (Box 19, Folder 427)
    - 620 - United States: State Department: General, 1944-1952 (Box 19, Folder 428)
    - 621 - Rockefeller Foundation Policy, RE: Communism, 1925-1952 (Box 20, Folder 429A)
    - 621 - Rockefeller Foundation Policy, RE: Communism, 1925-1952 (Box 20, Folder 429B)
    - 630 - Social Sciences: Divisional Correspondence, 1936-1952 (Box 20, Folder 430)
    - 630A - Social Sciences: Staff Meeting Minutes, 1948-1952 (Box 20, Folder 431)
    - 632 - Humanities: Divisional Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 20, Folder 432)
    - 650 - Russia: Miscellaneous (General), 1930-1952 (Box 20, Folder 433)
    - 651 - Russia: Miscellaneous Contacts with Russians, 1929-1939 (Box 20, Folder 434)
    - 651A - Russia: Miscellaneous Contacts with Russians, 1941-1951 (Box 20, Folder 435)
    - 652 - Russia: Miscellaneous (Social Sciences), 1934-1952 (Box 20, Folder 436)
    - 654 - Russia: Miscellaneous: Medical Sciences, 1932-1952 (Box 21, Folder 437)
    - 655 - Russia: Miscellaneous: Division of Humanities, 1943-1952 (Box 21, Folder 438)
    - 656 - Russia: Fellowship Policy 1927-1935, 1927-1952 (Box 21, Folder 439)
    - 660 - Europe: General, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 440)
    - 660A - Europe: Social Studies, 1939-1952 (Box 21, Folder 441)
    - 660C - Europe: Humanities, 1943-1952 (Box 21, Folder 442)
    - 660D - Europe: Medicine and Public Health, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 443)
    - 661 - Yugosalvia: General, 1946-1952 (Box 21, Folder 444)
    - 661B - Yugoslavia: Natural Sciences, 1950-1952 (Box 21, Folder 445)
    - 661C - Yugoslavia: Humanities, 1938-1952 (Box 21, Folder 446)
    - 662B - Iron Curtain Countries: Natural Sciences, 1946-1952 (Box 21, Folder 447)
    - 662D - Iron Curtain Countries: Medicine and Public Health, 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 448)
    - 663 - Czechoslovakia: General, 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 449)
    - 663A - Czechoslovakia: Social Sciences, 1930-1948 (Box 21, Folder 450)
    - 663B - Czechoslovakia: Humanities, 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 451)
    - 664 - Poland: General, 1945-1948 (Box 21, Folder 452)
    - 664A - Poland: Social Sciences, 1934-1952 (Box 21, Folder 453)
    - 665 - Hungary: General, 1945-1952 (Box 21, Folder 454)
    - 666 - Sardinia: General, 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 455)
    - 668 - Formosa: General, 1930-1951 (Box 21, Folder 456)
    - 669 - Far East: Program and Policy, 1947-1952 (Box 21, Folder 457)
    - 670 - China: Program and Policy: General, 1932-1945 (Box 21, Folder 458)
    - 670A - China: Program and Policy: General: 1946 - 1952, 1934-1952 (Box 22, Folder 459)
    - 671 - China: Program and Policy: International Health Division, 1936-1952 (Box 22, Folder 460)
    - 672 - China: Miscellaneous: General, 1930-1952 (Box 22, Folder 461)
    - 672A - China: Miscellaneous: Humanities, 1943-1952 (Box 22, Folder 462)
    - 672B - China: Miscellaneous: Natural Sciences, 1931-1952 (Box 22, Folder 463)
    - 672C - China: Miscellaneous: Medicine and Public Health, 1946-1949 (Box 22, Folder 464)
    - 672D - China: Miscellaneous: Social Sciences, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 465)
    - 673 - China: Administration: 1948-1949, 1948-1952 (Box 22, Folder 466)
    - 674 - China Program: General, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 467)
    - 674A: China Program: General: Reports, 1931-1952 (Box 22, Folder 468)
    - 675 - China Program: Rural Reconstruction, 1934-1952 (Box 22, Folder 469)
    - 676 - China Program: Mass Education Movement, 1932-1952 (Box 22, Folder 470)
    - 676A - China Program: Mass Education Movement: Local Fellowships, 1936-1943 (Box 22, Folder 471)
    - 677 - China Program: Nankai University, 1935-1944 (Box 22, Folder 472)
    - 677A - China Program: Nankai University: Local Fellowships, 1936-1944 (Box 23, Folder 473)
    - 678 - China Program: University of Nanking, 1935-1945 (Box 23, Folder 474)
    - 678A - China Program: University of Nanking: Local Fellowships, 1939-1946 (Box 23, Folder 475)
    - 679 - China Programs: Yenching University, 1936-1943 (Box 23, Folder 476)
    - 679A - China Programs: Yenching University: Local Fellowships, 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 477)
    - 680 - China program: North China Council for Rural Reconstruction, 1937-1952 (Box 23, Folder 478)
    - 680A - China program: North China Council for Rural Reconstruction: Local Fellowships, 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 479)
    - 681 - China Program: National Central University, 1935-1937 (Box 23, Folder 480)
    - 682 - China Program: National Agricultural Research Bureau, 1935-1943 (Box 23, Folder 481)
    - 682A - China Program: National Agricultural Research Bureau: Local Fellowships, 1936-1941 (Box 23, Folder 482)
    - 683 - China Program: National Health Administration: National Institute of Health, 1935-1939 (Box 23, Folder 483)
    - 683A - China Program: National Health Administration: Local Fellowships, 1936-1941 (Box 23, Folder 484)
    - 684 - China Program: Ministry of Education: Commission on Medical Education, 1935-1938 (Box 23, Folder 485)
    - 684A - China Program: Ministry of Education: Local Fellowships, 1937-1942 (Box 23, Folder 486)
    - 685 - China Program: Fellowships: General, 1935-1952 (Box 23, Folder 487)
    - 686 - China: Fellowships: General, 1941-1949 (Box 23, Folder 488)
    - 686A - China: Fellowships: Natural Sciences, 1944-1952 (Box 23, Folder 489)
    - 686B - China: Fellowships: Humanities, 1937-1952 (Box 23, Folder 490)
    - 686C - Chinese Scholars: Special Grant in Aid Funds: 1944-1949, 1943-1952 (Box 23, Folder 491)
    - 686D - China: Fellowships: Social Sciences, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 492)
    - 687 - China: Research and Developmental Aid, 1929-1933 (Box 23, Folder 493)
    - 687A - China: Research and Developmental Aid, 1934-1940 (Box 23, Folder 494)
    - 688 - China Medical Board: Peking Union Medical College, 1928-1952 (Box 23, Folder 495)
    - 689 - China: Actions: Humanities: National Library of Peiping: Microfilm, 1936-1952 (Box 23, Folder 496)
    - 689A - University of Nanking: Cinematography: 1944, 1941-1952 (Box 23, Folder 497)
    - 689B - Yenching University: Chinese Philosophy: 1947, 1947-1952 (Box 23, Folder 498)
    - 689C - Yenching University: Bibliography: 1948, 1947-1952 (Box 23, Folder 499)
    - 689D - Peitang Library: College of Chinese Studies: 1947, 1938-1952 (Box 23, Folder 500)
    - 689E - University of Nanking: Language Teaching Equipment: 1947 - 1950, 1947-1952 (Box 23, Folder 501)
    - 690 - China: Actions: Natural Sciences: University of Nanking, 1933-1952 (Box 23, Folder 502)
    - 690A - China: Actions: Natural Sciences: Tsing Nua College, 1929-1931 (Box 23, Folder 503)
    - 690B - China: Actions: Natural Sciences: Fukien Christian University, 1929-1931 (Box 23, Folder 504)
    - 690C - China: Actions: Natural Sciences: Yenching University, 1929-1933 (Box 23, Folder 505)
    - 690D - China: Actions: Natural Sciences: Nankai University, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 506)
    - 690E - China: Actions: Natural Sciences: University of Chekiang, 1937-1948 (Box 24, Folder 507)
    - 691 - China: Actions: Social Sciences: Nankai University: Institute of Economics, 1931-1952 (Box 24, Folder 508)
    - 692 - China: Actions: Medical Sciences: National Chunking University: Medical School, 1948-1949 (Box 24, Folder 509)
    - 693 - China: Actions: International Health Division: Public Health Training institute, 1939-1953 (Box 24, Folder 510)
    - 693A - Provincial Health Administration of Szechuan, 1943-1952 (Box 24, Folder 511)
    - 693B - Malaria Studies, 1937-1952 (Box 24, Folder 512)
    - 694 - China Program: Associated Boards for Christian Colleges (Box 24, Folder 513)
    - 700 - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial: Study of Russian Revolutions, 1925-1952 (Box 24, Folder 514)
    - CMB 1A - China Medical Board: General: 1920-1930, 1926-1947 (Box 24, Folder 515)